Guide to the General Accounting Services, Yale University, Monthly Accounting Statements
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
General Accounting Services, Yale University, monthly accounting statements
1976-1999
RU 1091
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
52.75
(158 boxes)
The materials consist of microfiche copies of monthly accounting statements from General Accounting Services.
Yale University. Office of Finance and Administration
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-B (YRG 5-B), Accounting records and records of the Yale comptroller.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from General Accounting Services, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Biographical / Historical
General Accounting Operations & Development is responsible for overseeing Labor Distribution, Grants Management, and Accounts Receivable, in addition to the General Ledger. The department is also responsible for establishing processes to ensure the proper integration of accounting. Additional responsibilities of GA Services include: establish the University's accounting calendar and oversee posting/closing activities; develop reconciliation processes/procedures that ensure effective integration of financial transactions; maintain COA values including PSOO and PTAEO; establish electronic transaction processing standards; and design quality assurance programs.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of microfiche copies of monthly accounting statements from General Accounting Services.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Universities and colleges -- Accounting; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Finance; Yale University. Office of Finance and Administration
- Monthly accounting statements, 1976-1999; Accession 2009-A-114
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035.
  - 1976 December - 1977June (Box 1)
  - 1977 June - 1978 January (Box 2)
  - 1978 February - July (Box 3)
  - 1978 August - 1979 March (Box 4)
  - 1979 March - July (Box 5)
  - 1979 August - 1980 January (Box 6)
  - 1980 February - July (Box 7)
  - 1980 July - 1981 January (Box 8)
  - 1981 February - October (Box 9)
  - 1981 November - 1982 July (Box 10)
  - 1982 July - December (Box 11)
  - 1982 December - 1983 January (Box 12)
  - 1983 February (Box 13)
  - 1983 March - April (Box 14)
  - 1983 April - August (Box 15)
  - 1983 September - 1984 February (Box 16)
  - 1984 March - June (Box 17)
  - 1984 June - December (Box 18)
  - 1985 January - February (Box 19)
  - 1985 March - April (Box 20)
  - 1985 May - June (Box 21)
  - 1985 June (Box 22)
  - 1985 June - July (Box 23)
  - 1985 August - September (Box 24)
  - 1985 October - November (Box 25)
  - 1985 November - December (Box 26)
  - 1986 January - June (Box 27)
  - 1986 June - September (Box 28)
  - 1986 October (Box 29)
  - 1986 November - December (Box 30)
  - 1986 December - 1987 April (Box 31)
  - 1987 May - June (Box 32)
  - 1987 June - October (Box 33)
  - 1987 October - 1988 February (Box 34)
  - 1988 February - May (Box 35)
  - 1988 May - July (Box 36)
  - 1988 August - September (Box 37)
  - 1988 October - November (Box 38)
  - 1988 November - December (Box 39)
  - 1989 January - May (Box 40)
  - 1989 June - August (Box 41)
  - 1989 August - 1990 January (Box 42)
  - 1990 February - May (Box 43)
  - 1990 June - 1991 March (Box 44)
  - 1991 April - December (Box 45)
  - 1992 January - April (Box 46)
  - 1992 May - June (Box 47)
  - 1992 July (Box 48)
  - 1992 August (Box 49)
  - 1992 September (Box 50)
  - 1992 October (Box 51)
  - 1992 November (Box 52)
  - 1992 December (Box 53)
  - 1993 January (Box 54)
  - 1993 February (Box 55)
  - 1993 March (Box 56)
  - 1993 April (Box 57)
  - 1993 May (Box 58)
  - 1993 June (Box 59)
  - 1993 June - 1st balance (Box 60)
  - 1993 June - 2nd balance (Box 61)
  - 1993 June - 3rd balance (Box 62)
  - 1993 June - 4th balance (Box 63)
  - 1993 July (Box 74)
  - 1993 August (Box 64)
  - 1993 September (Box 65)
  - 1993 October (Box 66)
  - 1993 November (Box 67)
  - 1993 December (Box 68)
  - 1994 January (Box 69)
  - 1994 February (Box 70)
  - 1994 March (Box 71)
  - 1994 April (Box 72)
  - 1994 May (Box 73)
  - 1994 June (Box 75)
  - 1994 June - 1st balance (Box 76)
  - 1994 June - 2nd balance (Box 77)
  - 1994 June - 3rd - 4th balance (Box 78)
  - 1994 July (Box 79)
  - 1994 August (Box 80)
  - 1994 September (Box 81)
  - 1994 October (Box 82)
  - 1994 November (Box 83)
  - 1994 December (Box 84)
  - 1995 January (Box 85)
  - 1995 February (Box 86)
  - 1995 March (Box 87)
  - 1995 April (Box 88)
  - 1995 May (Box 89)
  - 1995 June (Box 90)
  - 1995 June - 1st balance (Box 91)
  - 1995 June - 2nd balance (Box 92)
  - 1995 June - 3rd - 4th balance (Box 93)
  - 1995 July (Box 94)
  - 1995 August (Box 95)
  - 1995 September (Box 96)
  - 1995 October (Box 97)
  - 1995 November (Box 98)
  - 1995 December (Box 99)
  - 1996 January (Box 100)
  - 1996 February (Box 101)
  - 1996 March (Box 102)
  - 1996 April (Box 103)
  - 1996 May (Box 104)
  - 1996 June (Box 105)
  - 1996 June - 1st balance (Box 106)
  - 1996 June - 2nd balance (Box 107)
  - 1996 June - 3rd - 4th balance (Box 108)
  - 1996 July (Box 109)
  - 1996 August (Box 110)
  - 1996 September (Box 111)
  - 1996 October (Box 112)
  - 1996 November (Box 113)
  - 1996 December (Box 114)
  - 1997 January (Box 115)
  - 1997 February (Box 116)
  - 1997 March (Box 117)
  - 1997 April (Box 118)
  - 1997 May (Box 119)
  - 1997 June (Box 120)
  - 1997 June - 1st balance (Box 121)
  - 1997 June - 2nd balance (Box 122)
  - 1997 June - 3rd balance (Box 123)
  - 1997 June - 4th balance (Box 124)
  - 1997 July (Box 125)
  - 1997 August (Box 126)
  - 1997 September (Box 127)
  - 1997 October (Box 128)
  - 1997 November (Box 129)
  - 1997 December (Box 130)
  - 1998 January (Box 131)
  - 1998 February (Box 132)
  - 1998 March (Box 133)
  - 1998 April (Box 134)
  - 1998 May (Box 135)
  - 1998 June (Box 136)
  - 1998 June - 1st balance (Box 137)
  - 1998 June - 2nd balance (Box 138)
  - 1998 June - 3rd balance (Box 139)
  - 1998 June - 4th balance (Box 140)
  - 1998 July (Box 141)
  - 1998 August (Box 142)
  - 1998 September (Box 143)
  - 1998 October (Box 144)
  - 1998 November (Box 145)
  - 1998 December (Box 146)
  - 1999 January (Box 147)
  - 1999 February (Box 148)
  - 1999 March (Box 149)
  - 1999 April (Box 150)
  - 1999 May (Box 151–152)
  - 1998 June (Box 153–154)
  - 1998 June - 1st balance (Box 155)
  - 1998 June - 2nd balance (Box 156)
  - 1998 June - 3rd balance (Box 157)
  - 1998 June - 4th balance (Box 158)